http://www.bluecoats.com/privacy-policy

Volunteer
Bluecoats Logo, Visual Image, Website and Privacy PoliciesPurposeThis policy was developed for the Bluecoats Drum and Bugle Corps, Inc. because the verbal, written, photographic, artistic, and audio-visual images representing the organization are fundamentally linked to the public’s perception of the organization and to its overall success.Bluecoats recognize the significant role that visual depictions of the organization’s programs play in serving its public relations, merchandise sales, support, and recruitment needs and has developed these guidelines to facilitate consistent procedures for the appropriate use of the Bluecoats logo, marks, images, messages, and descriptions.The intent of this policy is to ensure that all imprinted items—drawn, printed, electronic, or web-based documents—and other visual representations identified with the Bluecoats:Present a consistent, professional, and constructive representation of the organization;Accurately represent the past, present, and future integrity of the organization;Comply with all national, state, or local, legal and ethical standards, including laws and policies governing copyright, libel, sexual harassment, and other content related issues; andMeet the standards, practices, and policies of the Bluecoats, and Drum Corps International, regarding the use of the organization name and logo.MERCHANDISE, PRINTED & IMPRINTED ITEMSAll logos, graphics, photographs, and renderings of the organization or its uniformed performing members are protected by U.S. and international copyright laws, and are the property of the Bluecoats Drum and Bugle Corps. All rights are reserved. Use of the Bluecoats logo and images without the expressed written permission of the Bluecoats is strictly prohibited.The Bluecoats maintain exclusivity of their souvenir and logo imprinted merchandise. Independent production, exhibition, or merchandising of souvenir or promotional items bearing copyrighted Bluecoats images is subject to criminal liability and prosecution.Requests for written permission to use the copyrighted logos and images of the Bluecoats may be addressed to the Board of Directors or to the Executive Director.Member created designs for section T-shirts, shorts, clothing, and other unofficial memorabilia items should comply with these guidelines; be pre-approved; and all production of said items be coordinated through the Bluecoats souvenir sales staff.Official Bluecoats WebsiteThe official Home Page of the Bluecoats on the World Wide Web is the document located at http://www.bluecoats.comThe Board of Directors, the CEO, and the organization’s webmaster share joint responsibility for the general appearance, content, maintenance, and updating of the official Bluecoats website. The Board of Directors shall maintain final responsibility for the resolution of any or all disputes related to website content and design.Statement of Website Domain Name OwnershipThe Bluecoats organization, not any individual, regardless of receipt for payment of domain name registration, shall remain the official owner of the domain name http://www.bluecoats.com and shall reserve the right to determine both the Administrative and Technical contacts for the purpose of domain name registration.Definition of Official CommunicationMaterial posted to the web page at http://www.bluecoats.com shall be considered official communication and must adhere to organization publication policies if it meets all three of the following criteria:It appears on pages bearing the official Domain Name ( http://www.bluecoats.com ) of Bluecoats Drum and Bugle Corps;It is intended to convey a message to the public from the organization as a whole, or from the officers, instructional staff, or other individuals of the organization who have been authorized to submit such messages for posting through the submission procedures described in this document; andIt can be accessed by any member of the general public.Unofficial CommunicationThe following are not considered official communications of the Bluecoats:Text, images and material appearing on personal web pages; orMaterial posted by individuals affiliated with the organization on pages other than http://www.bluecoats.com that may include the organization name and logo (used with permission) but whose primary focus is to represent subsections of the organization and target their communication to those specific audiences.Unofficial material is the responsibility of the individual posting the information. Portions of the Bluecoats Logo, Visual Image, and Web Site Policy may be applied as a criterion to unofficial websites prior to having their direct link posted on the official Bluecoats website. This safeguard is necessary because links between the organization’s official site and the “approved” unofficial site appear to be seamless to outside users.Webmaster(s) and Web AuthorsThe webmaster shall be responsible for the operational and logistical activities required to maintain a continuous web presence for the organization and shall maintain servers, hardware, and operating/authoring software, or shall develop partnerships with outside organizations for the provision of such services.To ensure the accuracy of information, a consistent style and adherence to organization web policies, only a limited number of individuals will be given read/write access to the web server files. These individuals (web authors) are responsible for:Creating and maintaining a consistency of style for all official communication;Working independently, or with organization officers or staff to create and update official web pages;Working together with those submitting information, and reviewing all documents for accuracy and consistency of style;Placing completed and approved files on the web servers (where they will be available to the public); andRemoving expired, excess, or offensive content from the website.Individuals may be added to, or removed from, the approved read/write web authors list by the webmaster, The Board of Directors, or the Executive Director. The Executive Director and The Board of Directors shall be responsible for the appointment or removal of the webmaster.Legal and Ethical Standards and PracticesAny information accessible through the Bluecoats website at http://www.bluecoats.com whether official or unofficial, must conform to legal and ethical standards, including laws and policies governing copyright, libel, sexual harassment, and other content related issues. Information distributed on the organization website must be the intellectual property of the individuals submitting it and must not contain copyrighted material that has not been cleared by the copyright holder for distribution.Copyright and PermissionAll content included on the Bluecoats website is the property of the Bluecoats Drum and Bugle Corps, and is protected by US and international copyright laws. All rights are reserved. Materials copyrighted or trademarked by the Bluecoats, including, but not limited to, audio recordings, video recordings, logos, graphics, photographic images, print materials and service marks included on this site may not be used without expressed written permission from the Bluecoats. Text may be reprinted and distributed, but may not be altered. No graphics may be used without the permission of the Bluecoats.The Bluecoats may grant permission to use images or materials featured on the Bluecoats website on a case-by-case basis. Requests for permission must be made in writing (or by e-mail) to the organization webmaster and must include the name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address of the individual responsible for maintaining the information on the unofficial site. The following disclaimer must be displayed on the homepage of an unofficial site using copyrighted items:Some copyrighted materials on this site are used with permission of the Bluecoats Drum & Bugle Corps. This site is not officially endorsed by or affiliated with the Bluecoats. Please visit the Official Bluecoats website at http://www.bluecoats.comAll original materials must be given appropriate credit. Video or still images must be credited to the photographer or video producer prior to publication.Web Policy UpdatesThe Bluecoats Board of Directors shall review this policy on an annual basis and recommend changes if warranted.Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter information on our site.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:• To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.• To improve our website in order to better serve you.• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.• To quickly process your transactions.• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.How do we protect visitor information?Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.We use regular Malware Scanning.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we use ‘cookies’?We do not use cookies for tracking purposesYou can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.However, you can still place orders.Third Party DisclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.GoogleGoogle’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=enWe have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpufAccording to CalOPPA we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymouslyOnce this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:• On our Privacy Policy PageUsers are able to change their personal information:• By logging in to their accountHow does our site handle do not track signals?We don’t honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. We don’t honor them because:Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?It’s also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral trackingCOPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.We do not specifically market to children under 13.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:We will notify the users via email• Within 7 business daysWe also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.  If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us atand we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.Bluecoats Drum & Bugle Corps, Inc.PO Box 2733N Canton, OH 44720bluecoats@bluecoats.com(330) 433-9115
VIEW ALL PERFORMANCE PARTNERS HERE
Cart (0)
